So how did you get to work today?
所以 今天你要怎样去上班？
&gt;&gt; I have a bike, works out just fine.
我有一辆自行车
How about you?
你呢？
&gt;&gt; Okay. I drive.
好的 我开车去
&gt;&gt; Oh cool, how's that car working out?
酷 你的车怎么样？
&gt;&gt; It's good.
很好
&gt;&gt; Yeah? Do you know how it works,
是吗？你知道在汽车的内部
underneath the hood?
是如何工作的吗？
&gt;&gt; No, I don't need to.
不 我不需要知道
I just need to put the key in, and then I drive it.
我只要把钥匙插进去 然后开走它
You know, this is kind of like writing code.
要知道 这就像是写代码
&gt;&gt; In what way?
哪里像？
&gt;&gt; Well, everything is kind of like writing code.
每一件事都有点像编写代码
&gt;&gt; Okay, yeah. &gt;&gt; Stick with me for a second.
- 好吧 - 继续听我说
In previous lessons we gave students a bunch of code.
在之前的课里 我们给学生们很多的代码
&gt;&gt; Yeah. We gave them methods like the display
是 我们给他们一些方法
method and the display price method.
像 display 方法和 display price 方法
&gt;&gt; Right. And we kept saying,
对 我们不停地说
well, don't worry about this.
好了 不要担心这个
We'll talk about what it does later.
我们将讨论它之后会做什么
Well that later is now.
就是现在
&gt;&gt; Okay.
- 好 - 好
So much like you know how a car works.
所以 就像你知道汽车是如何工作的
You can use it.
你可以利用这些
Students were able to use that method.
学生能够使用那个方法
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; Right?
- 好 - 对吗？
But we wrote the method, so we were
但是我们写这个方法 所以在这种情况下我们是汽车的设计者
the designers of the car in that case. &gt;&gt; I see.
我明白了
So the main idea is that you can define the method somewhere.
所以主要的思想是你可以在某处定义你的方法
&gt;&gt; So that's like building the car.
这看起来就像制造汽车
&gt;&gt; And then later you can call that method.
之后我们调用这个方法
&gt;&gt; That's like driving the car.
这就像开车一样
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是啊
&gt;&gt; So let's use those ideas next.
接下来让我们使用这些思想
&gt;&gt; Sounds good.
听起来不错
&gt;&gt; Within the MainActivity.java file,
在 MainActivity.java 文件里
this is where the display method is defined.
display 方法在此定义
And this is where it's getting called, within the increment method and
这正是获取调用的地方 在 increment 方法
within the decrement method.
和 decrement 方法里
The instructions of the display method take in a number and
display 方法是获得一个整数
then display it on the screen.
在屏幕上显示它
Like this right here.
像右边这样
Instead of defining a method we can also just take the instructions inside of it
定义一个方法 我们也可以只复制讲师注释里的代码
by copying it and then pasting it where we called that method.
然后粘贴到调用它的方法里
And since number is not a variable here, we're going to change it to quantity.
因为 number 不是一个变量 我们要把它改为 quantity
If we want to do the same for
如果你也想在 increment 方法里做同样的工作
the increment method, we'd copy this code and then paste it up here.
复制这段代码 然后粘贴到这
So this code works the same as we had before, but
所以这段代码能够和之前一样有效运行
now we don't need the display method.
但是现在我们不需要 display 方法
The disadvantage to this implementation is that we have duplicate code
这样做的缺点就是在这两个方法里
in both methods.
会有重复的代码
Instead, if we define the display method and then we just call it by its name,
相反 如果我们定义 display 方法 然后我们只是通过它的名字调用它
then we can have less code which is better for the app.
对于应用来说较少的代码是更好的
I also want to show you something else that's cool.
我还会给你看一些其他看起来很酷的东西
Anytime you see a method, you can click on it and then right click.
当你看到一个方法 你可以点击它 然后点击右键
And then go to declaration, or Command + V if you're on a Mac.
找到 Declaration 或者如果你在一个 Mac 上可以 Command + V
This scrolls the file to where the method is defined.
这样就会滚动到方法被定义的地方
This is useful because then you can see the actual instructions that
这是有用的 因为你可以看到真实的指令
are contained within that method.
包含在方法里面
For other methods,
对于其他的方法
it may open up a declaration in the Android framework code.
它可能会打开一个声明 在 Android 框架代码里
This was written by the Android team, the TextView.java file.
这是 Android 团队编写的 TextView.java 文件
This shows that, even though things may look like magic,
这看起来像魔术
you can always trace it back to the lines of code where it was defined.
它显示你可以随时跟踪它回到它被定义的代码行
Either by you or by someone on the Android team.
无论是你还是 Android 团队里的某人
To help you understand the difference between defining versus calling
为了让你了解定义和调用之间的差别
a method, let's modify the main activity.
我们修改 MainActivity
We're going to change the way a method is defined by changing the name of
改变定义方法的方式
the display method to the name displayQuantity.
通过改变 display 方法的名为 displayQuantity
Then for calling this method, do we need to change anything about that code?
对于调用这个方法 我们需要对代码做哪些改变呢？
If these changes cause an error in your app, make sure to address that so
如果这些改变在你的应用上出错了 确定解决这些错误
that you can run the app on your phone again.
这样应用才能在你的手机上再次运行
Check these boxes when you're done.
当你完成后勾选这些复选框